{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"2300/19",
			"answer":"2300/19",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7467/85",
			"answer":"7467/85",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7254/78",
			"answer":"7254/78",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"5331/85",
			"answer":"5331/85",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"8027/42",
			"answer":"8027/42",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"8.066/7.4",
			"answer":"8.066/7.4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"345./66",
			"answer":"345./66",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"97.34/0.031",
			"answer":"97.34/0.031",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2898/4.2",
			"answer":"2898/4.2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7.066/74",
			"answer":"7.066/74",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}